Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reader Services Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Dept. of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, reader services records
1964-1998
RU 123
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
36
(56 boxes)
The records consist of administrative files concerning financial transactions, research forms, and shipping memoranda of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives at Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted to the office of origin only.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files concerning financial transactions, research forms, and shipping memoranda of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives at Yale University Library.
Archives; Libraries -- Special collections; Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Deposit tickets and sales tax reports, 1975-1980; Accession 19ND-A-133 (Box 1–2)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Photoduplication orders for publications, 1970-1974; Accession 19ND-A-135 (Box 1)
- Call slips, 1964-1982; Accession 19ND-A-136 (Box 1–31)
- Photo order logbook, 1980-1983; Accession 19ND-A-137
  - Photo order logbook, 1980-1983 (Box 1)
- Cash Log Books, 1975-1980; Accession 19ND-A-415 (Box 1)
- Photo orders, invoices, research requests, 1981-1983; Accession 1983-A-095 (Box 1)
- Records, Accession 1983-A-096
- Mail order correspondence and photo orders, 1980-1982; Accession 1983-A-115 (Box 1–2)
- Call slips for manuscripts, 1982-1983; Accession 1984-A-058 (Box 1–2)
- Call slips for books, 1982-1983; Accession 1984-A-059 (Box 1)
- Call slips for microfilm, 1982-1983; Accession 1984-A-060 (Box 1)
- Photoduplication files, 1983-1984; Accession 1985-A-050 (Box 1)
- Call slips for manuscripts, 1984-1985; Accession 1985-A-051 (Box 1–2)
- Call slips for books and microfilm, 1984-1985; Accession 1985-A-053 (Box 1–2)
- Call slips for books and microfilm, 1983-1984; Accession 1985-A-054 (Box 1)
- Photoduplication files, circa 1983-1985; Accession 1985-A-055
  - Photographic services logbook, 1973-1981 May 27 (Box 1)
  - Xerox logbook, 1978 April 21-1980 September 12 (Box 1)
  - Photographic order log book, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Xerox logbook, 1975 November 11-1978 Apr21 (Box 2)
  - Completed photo book orders, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Completed tax reports, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Deposit tickets, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Accounting transfers, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Completed office of origin requests, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - FBI, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Invoice log, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Administrative and preservation xeroxing logs, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Photo order correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9-15)
  - Photo order correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photo order correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17-23)
- Call slips, 1997-1998; Accession 1999-A-058 (Box 1–2)
- Photoduplication logs, 1990-1998; Accession 2001-A-068
  - 1990-1992 (Box 1)
  - 1993-1995 (Box 2)
  - 1996-1998 (Box 3)